

Applicant for:

Software Engineer (PHP/ C#/.NET)

Starboard Asia Co.,ltd. 20 May 2020

Le Ba Tam

★ tamba43@gmail.com

Main interests: .NET, C#

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Le Ba Tam skipped the cover letter.

Le Ba Tam

Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam

tamba43@gmail.com, (+84)987499194

PROFILE

Total Experience (Years and Month)	8 years	DXC Experience (Years and Month)	4 years
Current Job Title	Software Engineer	Time in Current Role	8 years
Visa / Work permit	Viet Nam	Validity Date of Visa / Work Permit	N/A
Willing to Relocate	Yes	Willing to Travel	Yes

I joined DXC in February 2015 as Software Engineer for RSS project. This project used Window Form of C# to build software manage documents concern with medicines. I implemented functions by C#, wrote form which was used to display metadata, wrote Archive module which was used to archive documents, implemented validations to validate documents. From March 2016 to May 2017, implemented decoupling Logic and UI, refactored this software use WCF and unity.

Since June 2017, I joined Viewer team, implemented functions display information of medicine documents. Fixed bugs, deployed Viewer on IIS, deployed Viewer in QC environments, used telerik framework and ASP.net webform.

Before joining DXC, I worked as software engineer in Vn Resource.

SKILLS

Top Skills (Technical / Non Technical skills)

- C# (8 years)
- SQL Server (4 years)
- MVC (1 year)
- JQuery, telerik UI, kendo UI, material (2 years)
- Angular 5 (6 months)
- Java(hibernate, tomcat, jboss 5 months)
- Oracle(1 year)
- .Net core(1 month)

Revision Date: March 11 2019

- Sharepoint 2013 (2 months)
- Wordpress(2 months)
- HTML, CSS, Asp.net(3 years)

Key Roles Performed

• Software Developer – C# – 8 years

CERTIFICATIONS

PROFESSIONAL WORK EXPERIENCE

Global Cybersoft Dates

Manulife

December 2019 – May 2020

- Core responsibilities: Implement modules such as Chatbox(use MVC 3, PL/SQL), Procurement(use Sharepoint 2013), Business Insurance(use PL/SQL)
- Key achievements : finished task on time, met expectation

ST

March 2019 - December 2019

- Core responsibilities: Implement modules: export excel, handle security for WMA, send alarm/ack message when transfer data through ftp/sftp for WME, fix sonar issues, config WMA,WME.
- Key achievements: finished task on time, met expectation

DXC Technology Dates

Viewer

June 2017 – March 2019

- Core responsibilities :deployed website on QC environment, fixed bugs, implement new functions
- Key achievements: finished task on time, met expectations

TRS Feb 2015 – Jun 2017

- Core responsibilities: Implement modules: regional metadata, ich metadata, validation, archive, Publisher.
- Key achievements: finished task on time, met expectation

VN Resource 2010 - 2015

Revision Date: March 11 2019

Role

- Core responsibilities : developed e-commerce website, HR management, Hospital management
- Key achievements: finished task on time, met expectations

WORK REWARDS/ RECOGNITION

Name of the reward / recognition

EDUCATION

University

Nha Trang University Viet Nam

LANGUAGES

English - Read document, write email, use English, etc. : good

Revision Date: March 11 2019